Hi, my name's Dave Schoeneck, we're here in the beautiful Wasatch Mountains of Utah, here to talk about adaptive sports and how snowshoeing can fit in with a lot of people's adaptive life.
This is another good stretch, you just, athletic stance and reach towards each toe.
Hold it there, hold it there and then same thing, right side.
You really feel that in the hamstrings and in the glute muscles and that's a really an important muscle to stretch and get prepared because you'll be using that a lot.
You're going to want to get into your athletic stance, your feet are shoulders width apart and you're just going to bend down at the waist, following the legs down until you feel the stretch, reaching for those toes.
Reach, reach and you hold it, get as low as you can go and hold it and then try to go a little lower.
There you go.
This is really stretching the quad and you want to be straight up, this left leg straight, and then you're just pulling the right quad back until you just feel that burn, right there in the quad muscle.
Hold it, hold it as long as you can.
Then do the same thing with the other leg.
I'm kind of grabbing my ski pants.
You can grab your leg, it depends on how flexible you are.
I'm fairly flexible but I mentioned earlier, I have a prosthetic hip so I'm not as flexible as I used to be.